export const Questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "How do I assemble the product?",
    answer:
      "To assemble the product, follow the step-by-step instructions provided in the user manual. Make sure to use the included tools and follow safety precautions.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What are the recommended maintenance procedures?",
    answer:
      "Regular maintenance is important to ensure optimal performance. Clean the product with a mild detergent and soft cloth. Check for loose bolts and connections, and lubricate moving parts as instructed in the manual.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Can this product be used outdoors?",
    answer:
      "Yes, this product is designed for outdoor use. However, it's recommended to store it indoors or use a weather-resistant cover during extreme weather conditions.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What safety precautions should I take while using the product?",
    answer:
      "Always wear appropriate safety gear, such as gloves and eye protection. Keep hands and clothing away from moving parts. Read and follow all safety guidelines in the user manual.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "How do I adjust the settings for different levels of intensity?",
    answer:
      "You can adjust the intensity settings using the control panel or remote control, depending on the model. Refer to the user manual to understand the different settings and their effects.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the warranty period for this product?",
    answer:
      "The warranty period is usually stated in the user manual. It covers manufacturing defects and certain issues that may arise during normal usage. Contact our customer support for warranty-related inquiries.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Can I disassemble the product for storage?",
    answer:
      "Yes, most of our products can be partially disassembled for convenient storage. Follow the reverse steps of the assembly process to disassemble, and make sure to keep all parts in a safe place.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the maximum weight capacity of this product?",
    answer:
      "The maximum weight capacity is specified in the user manual. Exceeding this limit could lead to damage or instability. Make sure to adhere to the weight guidelines.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How do I troubleshoot if the product is not functioning?",
    answer:
      "First, check the power source and ensure all connections are secure. Consult the troubleshooting section of the user manual for common issues and solutions. If problems persist, contact our support team.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Is there any recommended storage procedure for the off-season?",
    answer:
      "During the off-season, it's advisable to clean the product thoroughly, lubricate any necessary parts, and store it in a dry, covered area. Follow the storage guidelines in the user manual.",
  },
];
